{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51623052","name":"Olin","address":"23 E Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Shawn & Holly McClain","licenseNumber":"PR19087C","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.04852,42.33425","geojson":{"id":"51623052","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.048519691,42.33425142]},"properties":{"name":"Olin","owner":"Shawn & Holly McClain","address":"23 E Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"PR19087C","establishmentid":"51623052","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"9/9/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622886","name":"Shinola Hotel- Evening Bar","address":"1400 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622702","name":"Shinola Hotel- WW Basement Kitchen","address":"1400 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622701","name":"Shinola Hotel- Banquet Kitchen","address":"1400 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622703","name":"Shinola Hotel-Birdie Room","address":"1400 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622882","name":"Penny Red's","address":"1400 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622881","name":"Shinola Hotel- San Morello","address":"1400 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622787","name":"The Brakeman","address":"1400 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","address":"34 W Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622763","name":"Cannelle Detroit LLC","address":"45 W Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622901","name":"Madcap Coffee Company","address":"1413 Farmer Street","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"52772","inspectionDate":"2020-09-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-306.11","violationDescription":"Except for nuts in the shell and whole, raw fruits and vegetables that are intended for hulling, peeling, or washing by the CONSUMER before consumption, FOOD on display shall be protected from contamination by the use of PACKAGING; counter, service line, or salad bar FOOD guards; display cases; or other effective means. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food on display","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lacking protection","subProblem":"Sneeze guards","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice holding bin","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-301.14","violationDescription":"Ventilation hood systems and devices shall be sufficient in number and capacity to prevent grease or condensation from collecting on walls and ceilings.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation hood","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Spaced more than 1/32 of an inch from adjoining","subProblem":"","location":"SERVER STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"holes or gaps along floors","problemDescription":"Not tight-fitting","subProblem":"Gaps greater than 1/16 of an inch","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor material(s)","subItem":"for construction","problemDescription":"Not nonabsorbent in areas subject to moisture","subProblem":"Food preparation","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Spaced more than 1/32 of an inch from adjoining","subProblem":"","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not attached","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (1st FLOOR)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR AND WALLS","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"WAREWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51623052"}}